Guide to the Leo K. Bustad Papers 1912-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Professional Papers
  - Subseries 2.3: People-Pet Partnership
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program photography contest, 1985-1987 (Folder 16, Item 194)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program "funny farm", 1974-1987 (Folder 16, Item 195)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program emblems and logos, 1984-1990 (Folder 16, Item 196)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program human-animal bond, 1982-1986 (Folder 16, Item 197)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program history of the human-animal bond, 1912-1982 (Folder 17, Item 198)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program arts and literature depicting the human-animal bond, circa 1400-1979 (Folder 17, Item 199)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program adults and animals, 1980-1987 (Folder 17, Item 200)
    - Slides People-Pet Partnership Program children and animals, 1952-1990 (Folder 17, Item 201)
    - "To Leo Bustad from Your Fan Club" in celebration of the first 10 years of People-Pet Partnership, 1990 April (Folder 18, Item 202)
  - Subseries 2.4: Human-Animal Bond
    - The inaugural seminar of the Joint Committee on Pets in Society, 1980 September 03 (Folder 19, Item 203)
    - Centre progresif de comportment animal, 1988-1989 (Folder 19, Item 204)
    - Dr. Aaron Katcher/human animal bond, 1980-1995 (Folder 19, Item 205)
    - Prison Pet Partnership (1 of 2), 1983-1998 (Folder 19, Item 206)
    - Prison Pet Partnership (2 of 2), 1983-1998 (Folder 20, Item 207)
    - Society for Companion Animal Studies, 1986-1995 (Folder 20, Item 208)
    - Waltham award, 1992-1996 (Folder 20, Item 209)
    - Japanese Animal Hospital Association, 1992-2005 (Folder 20, Item 210)
    - Latham Foundation, 1977-2004 (Folder 20, Item 211)
    - Konrad Lorenz/human animal bond, 1983-1989 (Folder 20, Item 212)
    - Man and Beast Revisted, 1985-1986 (Folder 20, Item 213)
    - McCulloch, Michael and Bill/human animal bond, 1980-1987 (Folder 20, Item 214)
    - People-Animals-Love (PALS), 1987-1994 (Folder 20, Item 215)
    - Hill's Pet Products, 1984-1996 (Folder 20, Item 216)
    - History of human animal bond/Konrad Lorenz, 1983 October (Folder 21, Item 217)
    - Human-Animal Bond Association of Canada, 1988-1989, 1996 (Folder 21, Item 218)
    - Human-Animal Bond in Tennessee, 1990-1996 (Folder 21, Item 219)
    - Handi-Dogs, Inc, 1983-1991 (Folder 21, Item 220)
    - Lynette A. Hart/human animal bond, 1983-1995 (Folder 21, Item 221)
    - Rough draft: "Hearing Dogs: An Experiment in Training" by Terry Ryan, Linda M. Hines and Leo K. Bustad, undated (Folder 21, Item 222)
    - History of human animal bond, 1980-1993 (Folder 21, Item 223)
    - Hills and People Pet Partnership Program, 1985-2001 (Folder 21, Item 224)
    - History of Animal Assisted Therapy (1 of 2), 1978-1990 (Folder 21, Item 225)
    - History of Animal Assisted Therapy (2 of 2), 1978-1990 (Folder 21, Item 226)
    - History of first conference on human animal bond (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Folder 21, Item 227)
    - History of first conference on human animal bond (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Folder 22, Item 228)
    - American Association of Animal Welfare Veterinarians Leo K. Bustad membership card, 1976 (Folder 22, Item 229)
    - People, Animals and Nature (P.A.N.), 1997 (Folder 22, Item 230)
    - Boris Levinson/human animal bond, 1971-1989 (Folder 22, Item 231)
    - Psychologists for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (Psy ETA), 1987 (Folder 22, Item 232)
    - Preliminary program outline Veterinary Medicine Section/Association of Military Surgeons of the United States (AUSUS), 1980 (Folder 22, Item 233)
    - Photographs Lynn Anderson/human animal bond, 1986-1987 (Folder 22, Item 234)
    - Photograph Robert K. Anderson 1987 Bustad Companion Animal Veterinary Award winner (Folder 22, Item 235)
    - American Minor Breeds Conservancy, 1986 (Folder 22, Item 236)
    - Angus Center/Human Animal Bond in Colorado, 1993-1999 (Folder 22, Item 237)
    - Animal Assisted Therapy Foundation International (AATFI), 1992 (Folder 22, Item 238)
    - Animals in Society guest edited by Leo Bustad and Linda Hines, 1986 (Folder 22, Item 239)
    - Guidelines: Animals in Nursing Homes, 1983 (Folder 22, Item 240)
    - Anthrozoos, 1997 (Folder 22, Item 241)
    - Alan M. Beck/Center for the Interaction of Animals and Society, 1980-1982 (Folder 22, Item 242)
    - British Columbia Society for Human/Animal Interaction, 1990-1991 (Folder 22, Item 243)
    - British Small Animal Veterinary Association, 1974 (Folder 22, Item 244)
    - Bruce Fogle/human animal bond, 1983-2003 (Folder 22, Item 245)
    - Group for the Study of the Human Animal Bond, 1979-1981 (Folder 22, Item 246)
    - American Anti-Vivisection Society advertisement/Daily Evergreen, 1975 March 11 (Folder 22, Item 247)
    - Leo K. Bustad brief biography, 1980 November (Folder 22, Item 248)
    - Photograph California Polytechnic State University Veterinary Science Club "In appreciation to Leo K. Bustad, DVM", 1992 (Folder 22, Item 249)
  - Subseries 2.5: Washington State University
    - Butch the cougar, 1978-1979 (Folder 22, Item 250)
    - Diamond jubilee/College of Veterinary Medicine, 1974 (Folder 22, Item 251)
    - Washington State University Building Dedications, 1978-1979 (Folder 23, Item 252)
    - Bustad Hall dedications, 1978, 1985 (Folder 23, Item 253)
    - Washington State University "Caring Call", 1990-1991; 1996 (Folder 23, Item 254)
    - Leo K. Bustad Endowed Fund, 1983-2004 (Folder 23, Item 255)
    - Work-related slides, 1987-1991 (Folder 23, Item 256)
    - Professional/Work-related photographs, 1949-circa 1990s (Folder 23, Item 257)
    - Professional/Work-related photographs, 1950s-circa 1990s (Folder 23, Item 258)
    - Professional/Work-related photographs, 1976-1989 (Folder 23, Item 259)
    - "The State College of Washington: the Campus in June", 1919 July (Folder 23, Item 260)
    - "Never Bug a Beagle: Progress Report '70", 1970 (Folder 23, Item 261)
    - Dr. Leo K. Bustad's Centaur yearbook, University of California, Davis, 1969 (Folder 23, Item 262)
    - Washington State University Vetrospect yearbook, 1974 (Folder 23, Item 263)
    - Washington State University Vetrospect yearbook, 1975 (Folder 23, Item 264)
    - Washington State University Vetrospect yearbook, 1976 (Folder 23, Item 265)
  - Subseries 2.6: Speeches
    - Abstract: Comparative Medicine: Long-range Goals and Considerations, 1973 July (Folder 24, Item 266)
    - Acceptance of the Delta Society Distinguished Service Award, 1990 October 12 (Folder 24, Item 267)
    - Acknowledgements (and apologies), undated (Folder 24, Item 268)
    - Adversity: A Severe, but Vital Taskmaster, 1985 July 14 (Folder 24, Item 269)
    - American Association of Human-Animal Bond Veterinarians, 1993 July 20 (Folder 24, Item 270)
    - Animal Contributions to the Health and Well-being of People, especially the Aging, 1980 September 03 (Folder 24, Item 271)
    - Animal-Facilitated Therapy, 1986 November 01 (Folder 24, Item 272)
    - Animals in Prison, undated (Folder 24, Item 273)
    - Auxilery Strategies for Increasing Awareness of the Relation of People and Pets, 1986 November 01 (Folder 24, Item 274)
    - Basic Qualities of Leadership, 1983 October 05 (Folder 24, Item 275)
    - Benefits of Animal Association for Disabled People, 1989 May 12 (Folder 24, Item 276)
    - Bethel - An Institution Without Walls, undated (Folder 24, Item 277)
    - The Benefits of Interactions of Children and Animals, 1992 April 24-25 (Folder 24, Item 278)
    - The Biology of the Pig, undated (Folder 24, Item 279)
    - Bustad's 10 Laws and the Royal Law, undated (Folder 24, Item 280)
    - Celebrating Freedom, undated (Folder 24, Item 281)
    - The Challenges and Impact of Current Bioethical and Biotechnical Revolutions For All of Us, 1983 April 15 (Folder 24, Item 282)
    - Challenges, 1981 August (Folder 24, Item 283)
    - Challenges for Veterinarians, undated (Folder 24, Item 284)
    - Choosing the Experimental Subject and its Environment, 1968 April 29-May 01 (Folder 24, Item 285)
    - Commitment to Compassion and the Community, 1981 January 08 (Folder 24, Item 286)
    - Companion Animals and the Aged, undated (Folder 24, Item 287)
    - Comparative Medicine: Studies in Animals for the Benefit of Animals and People, 1978 January 30 (Folder 24, Item 288)
    - Compassion, Freedom, Truth and Honor, 1977 August 05 (Folder 24, Item 289)
    - Compassion in Contemporary Society, undated (Folder 24, Item 290)
    - Compassion: Our Last Great Hope?, 1981 June 13 (Folder 24, Item 291)
    - Complex Problems and Humane Technology, undated (Folder 24, Item 292)
    - Concepts of Research from an Old Researcher, 1977 March 05 (Folder 24, Item 293)
    - Concern for the Handicaped, 1981 August (Folder 24, Item 294)
    - Convictions, undated (Folder 24, Item 295)
    - Creativity, 1970 April 21 (Folder 24, Item 296)
    - Current Challenges in Comparative Medicine, 1979 March 26 (Folder 24, Item 297)
    - Curriculum to Promoate Greater Understanding of the Human-Companion Animal Bond, 1980 January 24-25 (Folder 24, Item 298)
    - Dean's Presentation to Faculty and Staff on the State of the College, 1982 October 21 (Folder 24, Item 299)
    - Dedication Address, 1978 October 20 (Folder 24, Item 300)
    - Delta Conference Notes: President's Award, undated (Folder 24, Item 301)
    - Death and Grief and its Relief, 1986 March 01 (Folder 24, Item 302)
    - Effective Listening, undated (Folder 24, Item 303)
    - Effects of Single or Fractionated X-irradiation and of Bone-seeking Radionuclides on Mammals: A Review, 1969 March 06 (Folder 24, Item 304)
    - Emphasizing the Positive, 1981 January (Folder 24, Item 305)
    - Encountering the Future, 1978 June 08 (Folder 24, Item 306)
    - Enhancement of the Human/Animal Bond, 1983 April 09 (Folder 24, Item 307)
    - Enhancement of Our Understanding of the Human/Animal Bond, Aging and Grief, 1983 October 13 (Folder 24, Item 308)
    - Enhancing Understanding of Aging, Death and Handicaps in Our Clients and Patients, 1983 April 08-10 (Folder 24, Item 309)
    - Ethics and Values Portion of Professional Orientation, 1986 (Folder 24, Item 310)
    - The Experimental Subject: Care and Handling, 1980 June (Folder 24, Item 311)
    - Excellence in Teaching, Research, and Service in an Established School, 1978 November (Folder 24, Item 312)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1980 October 02 (Folder 24, Item 313)
    - The Five Bs - Out Biggest Future Problems/Diamond Jubilee, 1974 (Folder 24, Item 314)
    - Freedom and Responsibility, 1987 (Folder 24, Item 315)
    - Freedom, Honor and Integrity, 1980 September 06 (Folder 24, Item 316)
    - Future - Hope or Nightmare, 1979 December (Folder 24, Item 317)
    - Gerontologic Studies at the Radiobiology Laboratory, undated (Folder 24, Item 318)
    - Grief is the Price of Loving, 1984 December (Folder 24, Item 319)
    - Has Science and Technology Outlived Their Usefulness, undated (Folder 24, Item 320)
    - Health Benefits of Animals, 1988 July 19 (Folder 24, Item 321)
    - The Health Benefits of Cats, undated (Folder 24, Item 322)
    - Health Benefits of Human-Animal Interaction, 1990 April 28-29 (Folder 24, Item 323)
    - Health Benefits of Human-Animal Introduction, 1989 June 15 (Folder 24, Item 324)
    - Health Benefits of Pets: A Historical Perspective, 1987 September 10 (Folder 24, Item 325)
    - Hearing Ear Dogs for the Pet Set, undated (Folder 24, Item 326)
    - An Historic Perspective of Veterinary Medical Education, undated (Folder 24, Item 327)
    - The History of Human/Animal Interrelationships, 1986 November 01 (Folder 24, Item 328)
    - Holocaust: Lession for Healthcare Workers, undated (Folder 24, Item 329)
    - How Animals Make People Human and Humane, 1979 May (Folder 24, Item 330)
    - How Mice Can Help Cattle, 1981 December 11 (Folder 24, Item 331)
    - How Do We Feed All the People?, 1977 November 15 (Folder 24, Item 332)
    - Human/Animal Bond/James Law Auditorium, 1980 October 02 (Folder 24, Item 333)
    - Human-Animal Bond and Health Professionals, 1982 May 21 (Folder 24, Item 334)
    - The Human Animal Bond and Reverence for Life, 1986 September 19-21 (Folder 24, Item 335)
    - The Human-Animal Bond in the Public Health Curriculum, 1983 July 20 (Folder 24, Item 336)
    - The Human-Animal Bond: Our Profession's Responsibilities, 1987 August 18 (Folder 24, Item 337)
    - Human/Animal Interrelationship: Our Responsibilities to Our Animals, 1986 (Folder 24, Item 338)
    - Human-Companion Animal Bond and the Curriculum, 1980 January 24-25 (Folder 24, Item 339)
    - Human Companion Animal Bond: Animal-facilitated Therapy and the Responsibilities of Health Providers, 1982 November (Folder 24, Item 340)
    - Human Companion Animal Bond: The Veterinarian's Responsibility, 1981 April 30 (Folder 24, Item 341)
    - The Human Factor in Animal Research, 1986 February 28 (Folder 24, Item 342)
    - Human Health Concerns in Federal Veterinary Medicine, 1980 (Folder 24, Item 343)
    - The Human-Pet Relationship, 1983 October 27-28 (Folder 24, Item 344)
    - Humane Considerations in Our Profession, 1977 May 14 (Folder 24, Item 345)
    - Impact of History, Literature and Art on Teaching Reverence for Life, 1982 June 28 (Folder 24, Item 346)
    - The Impact of Humane Technology on Science and Us, 1972 January (Folder 24, Item 347)
    - The Impact of the Revolution That Is the Human/Animal Bond, 1983 July 18 (Folder 24, Item 348)
    - Improving Euthanasia: An Educator's Approach, undated (Folder 24, Item 349)
    - Inferences on Radiation Carcinogenesis Revealed by Selected Studies in Animals, 1975 April 07 (Folder 24, Item 350)
    - The Inner Ring, 1974 June 10 (Folder 24, Item 351)
    - Introduction of Dr. Michael DeBakey, 1983 August 03 (Folder 24, Item 352)
    - It's True, an Elephant Never Forgets, undated (Folder 24, Item 353)
    - Investigators' Interrelationship with Laboratory Animals, 1984 October 11-12 (Folder 24, Item 354)
    - Invitational Conference on Scientific Methodology for Research on the Interactions of Animals and People, undated (Folder 24, Item 355)
    - Is the Human Animal Bond Significant in Research?, 1985 October 01 (Folder 24, Item 356)
    - Laboratory Scientists and Their New Role in Human/Animal Bonding, 1983 August 04 (Folder 24, Item 357)
    - Legislative Advocacy, 1982 July 26 (Folder 24, Item 358)
    - Leo K. Bustad's response on receiving the World Small Animal Veterinary Association International Award for Service to the Profession, undated (Folder 24, Item 359)
    - Listening, 1974 September 15 (Folder 24, Item 360)
    - Llamas in Animal Assisted Therapy (AAT), undated (Folder 24, Item 361)
    - Maintaining Human and Humane Values in a Technological World, 1982 October 15 (Folder 24, Item 362)
    - Miniature Pigs in Research, 1967 February 04 (Folder 24, Item 363)
    - More Than Scholars, 1976 October (Folder 24, Item 364)
    - My General Philosophy, 1977 May 13 (Folder 24, Item 365)
    - My Laws on Leadership, 1987 March 27 (Folder 24, Item 366)
    - The National Advisory Committee - How You Effect It - How It Affects You, undated (Folder 24, Item 367)
    - Norway and the United Kingdom in May, undated (Folder 24, Item 368)
    - On Freedom and Honor, 1976 June 05 (Folder 24, Item 369)
    - On Grief and Joy, 1984 July 15 (Folder 24, Item 370)
    - On Leadership, 1979 May 17 (Folder 24, Item 371)
    - On Touch and Gentling, 1995 February 14 (Folder 24, Item 372)
    - Our Awesome Power Over Life and Death (Bio 85-Engineering Life), undated (Folder 24, Item 373)
    - Our Professional Responsibility Relative to Human-Animal Interactions, 1984 July 08 (Folder 24, Item 374)
    - Our Profession's Challenges and Responsibilities for Animal Well-Being and Bonding, 1985 February 15-17 (Folder 24, Item 375)
    - Our Role in the Human/Animal Bond and Promotion of Human Health and Well-Being, 1983 (Folder 24, Item 376)
    - Parathyroid Lecture/Physiological Sciences 140A, 1972 (Folder 24, Item 377)
    - People and Pets: A Positive Partnership, 1982 April (Folder 24, Item 378)
    - People-Animal Interaction - A Look Back - A Look Ahead, undated (Folder 24, Item 379)
    - Pet/Human Bond Workshop, 1982 June 07 (Folder 24, Item 380)
    - Pigs: From BC -2000 AD: From Outhouse to Penthouse, undated (Folder 24, Item 381)
    - Placement of Animal with the Elderly: Benefits and Strategies, 1981 October 06 (Folder 24, Item 382)
    - The Potential Contributions of Veterinary Medical Schools to the Programs of the Atomic Energy Commission, the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, and the Department of Defense, 1969 July 13 (Folder 24, Item 383)
    - Proposal for Governor's Seminars, 1979-circa 1980 (Folder 24, Item 384)
    - Qualities of Leadership as Elaborated by Bustad's Laws, 1985 March 28 (Folder 24, Item 385)
    - Quantitation of Bone Marrow Recovery Following Subletheal Irradiation in Beagles, 1969 August 25-29 (Folder 24, Item 386)
    - Radiation Tumorigenesis and Life Shortening, undated (Folder 24, Item 387)
    - The Reason that I'm Here…/Nuclear Medicine-Veterianary Medicine Las Vegas, undated (Folder 24, Item 388)
    - Recent Discoveries About Our Relationships with the Natural World, 1989 November 15-18 (Folder 24, Item 389)
    - Recommendations on Proposed Public Health Research on Volcanic Ash, undated (Folder 24, Item 390)
    - The Relief and Prevention of Grief, 1981 March 27-29 (Folder 24, Item 391)
    - A Report by Your Peripatetic Dean, undated (Folder 24, Item 392)
    - Responsibilities of Veterinarians Regarding Animal-Facilitated Therapy, undated (Folder 24, Item 393)
    - Reverence for Life, 1984 April 29 (Folder 24, Item 394)
    - Rx for Good Health: Take Home a Pet, 1988 (Folder 24, Item 395)
    - Charles R. Schroder, DVM - Doctor of Zoos, undated (Folder 25, Item 396)
    - Seems That Suffering Never Ends, 1981 July 15 (Folder 25, Item 397)
    - Shipping Out and Shaping Up, 1992 May (Folder 25, Item 398)
    - The Significance of Human Animal Bond to Veterinary Practice, 1986 November 08-09 (Folder 25, Item 399)
    - The Significance of Radionuclide Contamination in Ruminants, 1964 August 19-21 (Folder 25, Item 400)
    - Sitting vs. Jogging, 1980 January (Folder 25, Item 401)
    - Some Biomedical Applications of Radioisotopes, 1961 December (Folder 25, Item 402)
    - Some of My Laws, 1973 August 01 (Folder 25, Item 403)
    - State of the College, 1974 January (Folder 25, Item 404)
    - A Strong Human/Animal Bond is Critical to a Healthy Community, 1982 September 23 (Folder 25, Item 405)
    - Symposium Summary: International Symposium on Human-Pet Relationship, 1983 October 28 (Folder 25, Item 406)
    - Summary Remarks to the Energy Extention Conferees, 1979 August 07 (Folder 25, Item 407)
    - Tenure: Bane or Boon, 1972 January-March (Folder 25, Item 408)
    - Therapeutic Aspects of the Human-Animal Bond: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, undated (Folder 25, Item 409)
    - The 3 R's Are Not Enough, 1986 Septeber 18 (Folder 25, Item 410)
    - To Become One of Them, 1984 January 12 (Folder 25, Item 411)
    - Touch: A Matter of Life and Death, undated (Folder 25, Item 412)
    - Tribute to George Brain, 1986 October 03 (Folder 25, Item 413)
    - Tribute to Nobel Laureate Konrad Lorenz, undated (Folder 25, Item 414)
    - Understanding the Interaction of People, Animals and the Environment, undated (Folder 25, Item 415)
    - Untitled - South African Stories, 1969 April 10 (Folder 25, Item 416)
    - The Veterinarian and Animal-Facilitated Therapy, 1980 (Folder 25, Item 417)
    - Veterinary Medicine's Responsibilites to the Handicapped, undated (Folder 25, Item 418)
    - Volcanic Dust Summary for the Board of Regents, undated (Folder 25, Item 419)
    - Wegner Farm and Other Sheep-Related Research in Veterinary Medicine at Washington State University and the University of Idaho, 1981 November 06 (Folder 25, Item 420)
    - We Hear But We Don't Listen, 1980 July (Folder 25, Item 421)
    - What Is It Really Like To Be Hungry, 1981 May 12 (Folder 25, Item 422)
    - What's New, 1980 October 27 (Folder 25, Item 423)
    - Where Were You on June 6, 1944, 1994 June 03 (Folder 25, Item 424)
    - Where is Veterinary Medicine Going, 1974 July 21 (Folder 25, Item 425)
    - Writing Your Eulogy, 1985 May 11 (Folder 25, Item 426)
    - Witnessing: How To Tell a Story, 1987 March 15 (Folder 25, Item 427)
    - You Must Be More Than Scholars, 1984 June 09 (Folder 25, Item 428)
    - Zusammenfassung Des Symposiums (Summary of the Symposiums), undated (Folder 25, Item 429)
    - Zoos: A Brief Overview, 1991 November 21 (Folder 25, Item 430)
  - Subseries 2.7: Publications
    - Anatomical and Physiological Data in Miniature Swine, circa 1959 (Folder 25, Item 431)
    - Animal-Assisted Therapy, undated (Folder 25, Item 432)
    - Animal Models, 1977 (Folder 25, Item 433)
    - Animals, Aging, and the Aged, 1981 (Folder 25, Item 434)
    - Animals and Mental Health, undated (Folder 25, Item 435)
    - Animals' Contribution to Physical Health and Well-Being, 1979 August (Folder 25, Item 436)
    - Animals in Prisons, undated (Folder 25, Item 437)
    - The Art and Importance of Listening, undated (Folder 25, Item 438)
    - Biological Effects of I (131) Continously Adminstered to Sheep, 1957 March (Folder 25, Item 439)
    - Biological Effects of I (131) in Sheep and Swine, 1964 (Folder 25, Item 440)
    - Biological Implications of Atomic Test Fallout, 1955 (Folder 25, Item 441)
    - The Bond Between People and Their Animal Companions, 1982 Spring (Folder 25, Item 442)
    - Bridget's Last Ride, 1994 (Folder 25, Item 443)
    - The Choice of the Beagle in Radiobiologic Studies, 1972 (Folder 25, Item 444)
    - Choosing the Experimental Subject and its Environment, 1968 April (Folder 25, Item 445)
    - Clinical Applications of Research in a Large Beagle Colony, with Emphasis on Aging, 1973-1974 (Folder 25, Item 446)
    - Companion Animals in Human Health, 1997 (Folder 25, Item 447)
    - Compassion for Animals, 1986 Winter (Folder 25, Item 448)
    - Comparative Leukemia and Sarcoma Viral Studies, 1972 October 01 (Folder 25, Item 449)
    - Comparative Medicine: Progress and Prospects, 1976 (Folder 25, Item 450)
    - A Comparative Study of Hanford and Utah Range Sheep, 1953 (Folder 25, Item 451)
    - Creating Compassion for Animals, 1985 (Folder 25, Item 452)
    - Damage to Livestock from Radioactive Fallout in Event of Nuclear War, 1963 (Folder 25, Item 453)
    - Dean's Responsibilities and Bioethics, 1983 Spring (Folder 25, Item 454)
    - Development of Hanford Miniature Swine, 1965 July (Folder 25, Item 455)
    - Disease Experience with Miniature Swine, 1967 August (Folder 25, Item 456)
    - Diseases of the Pig, undated (Folder 25, Item 457)
    - Dose and Dose Rate Problems in Radiation Tumorigenesis, 1975 (Folder 25, Item 458)
    - An Educator's Approach to Euthanasia, 1982 May-June (Folder 25, Item 459)
    - Effects of Stable Iodine on Uptake of Radioiodine in Sheep, 1958 October (Folder 25, Item 460)
    - Effects of Mt. St. Helens Volcanic Eruption on Animals - Abstract, undated (Folder 25, Item 461)
    - Effects of Prolonged Low-Level Irradiation of Mice, 1965 (Folder 25, Item 462)
    - Effecting Healthcare Insurance Reform: Research on the Efficacy of Animal Assisted Therapies, 1995 (Folder 25, Item 463)
    - Evaluation of Long-Term Effects of Exposure to Internally Deposited Radionuclides - Corrected Abstract, undated (Folder 25, Item 464)
    - The Experimental Subject - A Choice, Not an Echo, 1970 (Folder 25, Item 465)
    - Freedom: Facing Up to Our Responsibility, 1976 February (Folder 25, Item 466)